Yeah!
Where are we going to film the opening? Can we do it now?
Oh, we already did it.
Oh, okay.
What's today?
I'm in Yeomemi.
We're at the aquarium!
Yay!
Aquarium
The aquarium at Sunshine Ikebukuro!
Yay!
I love aquariums.
I've been here a couple of times.
Oh, I see.
When I saw it, I thought, "I want to go to the aquarium.
And now I do!
Aquariums are great, aren't they?
It's been a long time since I've been here.
Let's have fun while talking about the dacoder
Let's go see it!
Yay!
We went together about 3 years ago, right? We did! We went to Enoshima!
Jellyfish are so cute here too, so I'm looking forward to seeing them!
Oh! Beautiful! It's nice. It's beautiful, isn't it?
Wow!
So cute!
I've been thinking about Ariel's...
Ariel?
The Ulman mask. The movie came out.Ulman's face, because the movie came out.
When I see something like this...
Ariel! I'm like...
I want to see Ariel.
I want to see Ariel!
It's like a phoenix.
It's such a beautiful space.
I love it.
Which one do you like?
Which one?
This one's cute.
He's really tiny.
Stripy?
Yes, he swims in a strange way.
He's cute down there.
You see it?
Who's my favorite?
Who's your favorite?
The red one.
It's huge.
You picked a great one.
He's cute.
What's this?
No?
It's your sister.
It was her.
I thought it was just a whisper.
It's not even close.
You're too big.Too big.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Thank you.
For cleaning me up.
Wow!
Yum!
Umaso is so good!
Kakimono.
Oysters...
Sardines!
Sardines and little chickens.
They're so soft and fluffy.
Where's the little chicken?
Oh, I don't know. They're all here.
They're here.
They're all here.
Oh, my God, they all look the same.
Oh, what the hell?
What the hell?
This is it.
A small stage.
Oh, my God! It was!
What!
It looks good.
Big!
Big! It's huge!
It's huge!
You see?You know what?
There's a better fish.
Is that different?
A little different.
Let's make it pretty.
Look, purple! It's this color.
4mm color.
I love the 4mm color!
The color of this one looks more like...
It's a little darker.
I can't even recognize it.
I can't look at it for the rest of my life.
It's so comforting.
There's an A, too.
A manta ray?
That sounds like an A.
We went fishing the other day.
I went fishing with the guys.
We were fishing for A.
You catch A's?
You fish for A's?
Yes! We're fishing for A.
Oh, my God! Are you going that way?
No?
Are we in the jellyfish zone?
No jellyfish zone!
This is the jellyfish zone I've been looking forward to the most!
No jellyfish!
He looks so sad.
Jellyfish!Jellyfish!
There's no jellyfish.
What are you doing?
Cleaning.
I'm cleaning.
I found jellyfish.
Cleaning about once every two years.
Cleaning once every 2 years
I could exhale.
But really, the jellyfish here are so beautiful.
Wow, I wish I could have seen them.
And here, the curtains are closed.
I guess it's supposed to be like this so you can get into the jellyfish space.
That's right.
So no other light can pass through.
It shines like a jewel.
That's why I want you to come and see it.
It was an impulse.
You're lucky.
I got lucky.
Lucky.
I'll never forgive you.
I won't forgive you.
You like jellyfish, don't you, Mr. Iro?
I love jellyfish.
This way... this way... this way...
This way!
Wait! Wait! Wait!Wait, wait, wait.
Could you come in here, please?
Not that way.
That way, that way.
Oh, my God, he's running.
Don't run.
Don't get married.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm a little excited.
Hey, there's a jellyfish.
Aren't they beautiful?
Look.
I'm married to a jellyfish.
It's like cheese.
It's so cute.
Oh, my God.
Oh, is that not a bit of a tie-in?
Oh, wow.
It gets tangled up sometimes, doesn't it?
Maybe.
Huh.
It's okay.
It's hard to tell how close they are.
Wow, I look good as a jellyfish.
What's that? What's that? There's one over there, too.
Let's go. Look.
Amazing!
The world of jellyfish!
What? Ariel!What? Ariel.
She makes everything look like Ariel.
She's so cute.
It looks like a flower.
It really is. It's a beautiful pattern.
It's so beautiful and cute!
I'm going to make a sound for Millimeter.
She's so full of energy.
It's moving like a baby!
Puff, puff, puff!
He's so cute! He's got so many legs!
He's so cute with his short legs.
And there's something else.
Oh, my God!
I feel like I'm in heaven.
That was fun. Jellyfish are the best.
Jellyfish Zone was fun, right?
Yeah, it was.
Blue Squid.
That's the good stuff, right?
It's delicious, isn't it?
The first thing I said when we walked in the aquarium...
I said, "It smells like sashimi.
That's all he could think about.
Isn't he cute?
It's like a pillow.
Jellyfish projection mapping.
Stairs.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is what I'm talking about.
That's great
Mimyan
That's good.
Oh, wow, that's good.
Big hand fry
So many people!
I don't know, it's just...
It's getting hard.
It's so hard!
Smells so good! It's an oasis of karat green!
It's an oasis. It's a big fish.
Is it there? Yes.
There it is, it's tiny, it's tiny, it's so healthy.
Look, look, look, look.
He's so cute.
Cute little blue one.
Wile!
It's not just the fish
Like this.
You'll be impressed.
I like the way he performs.
Too long beard!
Moko-chan!
I named him.
Sana's dog's name.
Grandma!Grandma.
Bunny.
Wow!
It's so beautiful here.
It's so beautiful.
It looks like it's painted with paint.
Rainbow colors
I love it.
It's outside!
Outside! Then, outside? Outside zone.
Oh! Oh, my gosh! It's huge! I'll give it a thumbnail chance.
You think it'll come? I like this one.
Do you think it'll come? It's coming! It's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming!
Oh, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming.
What? Where is it?
It's big.
It's huge.
Oh, wow.
It's so cute.
I wonder if he spins around like this all day long.
But it looks so comfortable.
I want to scratch my feet!
No kidding.
Penguins.
Penguin!
You look like Iori.
Why?
You look like him, bro.
Ioshan.
Oh, my God.Oh, my God.
He's baffled.
It really is.
Over there.
Oh, there he is! Pull, pull, pull, pull!
Cute.
Wow.
Too cute!
Are you in the hairy season? Like, hair-growing season?
That's right.
So this one that's growing hair right now is a rarity, right?
That's great.
It's time to grow back.
It's soothing.
Yeah, it is.
Oh, big!
It's so round!
That's a great feeling!
That's amazing! You're looking at it from a higher vantage point than anyone else.
Right!
Wow!
I'm here, but I can't see much!
Long beak!
Hey!
Isn't this pretty pink amazing?
It's amazing!
Look at me! Wave!
Give me a lesson!
Put it on my chest.On the chest.
Penguins.
They're swimming.
You're so energetic.
Penguins in the sky.
I want to swim.
Can you swim?
You can't swim?
You seem to be a much faster crawler than I am.
I'm a fast crawler.
I can only crawl.
He can only crawl.
He can do the breaststroke and butterfly.
I can't swim the breaststroke.
You can't swim? Surprising.
Listen...
I think I'm done.
I'm done.
And now...
I'd like to go to the blind reading room.
Let's go!
So cute!
Let's go in!
Let's go!
Oh! Poison Poison!
What about the ducts?
Hazardous to life and health.
What's that? Suddenly.
We're being poisoned.
They say there's a toxic level.Because they say there are poison levels.
Poison level three.
It's a jellyfish.
Wow, their color is different.
It's so weird.
Do 4 on this one, too.
It's so cute!
But I think there's 4 in there.
But isn't it amazing? What's with the polka dots?
Yeah, they're kind of...
It's like it's clearly a bad idea.
But it's cute.
Even though it's cute.
Hey...
Pennies.
It's so bad, I'm sure.
Oh, Tyber...
Which one?
Which one? The back one?
This is the one in the back, right?
Oh, this is one.
Oh, it looks like a rock back there.
A rock, huh? It looks like a rock.
It looks like a rock.
Close.
Is it okay to get this close?
Too close.
Is this fun? Oh, my God, Doktay.
It's fun.Fun.
Mushrooms.
Oh, mushrooms. Remember these.
This one...
This one looks like something I'd eat.
I'll definitely learn this one.
This one looks kind of bad.
But I think it looks delicious.
I'll remember it.
But it's 5.
I don't want to auto-do it.
This is obviously bad.
This is so bad.
This one's cute, too.
It's like a character.
I'd color it.
It's true.
It looks like a character.
It's cute, but...
This one is bad.
This one looks kind of tasty.
Looks like beef.
Yakiniku?
That's for sure.
It looks like yakiniku.
I'm hungry for yakiniku.
It makes me want to eat yakiniku.
Wait!
What?
Spider! Spider! Spider!Spider. Spider. Spider.
Look, I guessed it.
Oh, really?
Tell me, what did you guess?
I don't know!
Lias the bird eater.
Is it alive?
Is it a model?
What do you mean?
Is it alive?
I think it's alive.
I'm sending you a year.
Hello?
Oh, it's working.
I just got a jolt.
I'm getting through.
Oh, scary.
Oh, no.
Oh, it's not here.
There it is!
It's dangerous!
Slippery Manjuu
Thank you for watching!
I'm in love with something delicious.
Oh, no!
what is this?
Let's smell you, Simaskan-kun!Let's smell Mr. Simaskan!
Press the button
You can smell him.
If you sense any danger.
Get out of the booth as soon as possible.
Okay! You're coming with me.
No?
I'm coming with you.
Can you give me a push?
Do you want to keep going for a long time?
Yeah. - Okay.
Turn around.
Ready?
Aaah!
What?
You're wrong!
Huh?
What's that delicious smell?
It smells like garlic.
Like after eating jiro.
Ha-ha-ha.
Smells like...
Sounds delicious.
What?
Too heavy.
Aaah!Aaah!
Aaah!
Aah!
Buck!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Wait.
That's so gross!
Oh, no!
I can't get rid of the scent.
You're here all the time. You're here all the time.
You're here forever.
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta...
It's over. It's over.
I didn't expect it to end with the smell of stamps.
I'm still here. I'm hungry.
Yeah, when I said I wanted to eat meat...
It looks like we can go out for yakiniku.
Yay!
We'll go to the aquarium and Tonato and I will go eat yakiniku.
Okay, I'm off!